2modern.com 2017-10-04

# Privacy & Security Policy - 2Modern

**OUR PRIVACY POLICY  
**Last updated:  May 15, 2017

2Modern, an online website accessible at www.2Modern.com (the “Website”) recognizes that you care how information about you is used and shared and we respect your privacy. This Privacy Policy describes the information we may collect from you, how we collect that information, how we use that information, and your choices with respect to how your information is collected and used. By using our website, mobile applications, or providing information to us, you agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy. 

  This Privacy Policy was last updated May 15, 2017, and may be updated from time to time. Please check back periodically for further updates and changes to the Privacy Policy. The most updated version will be available on our website.

**WHAT INFORMATION ABOUT ME IS COLLECTED AND STORED?  **

  **Information Provided by You  **

  We collect and store information that you provide to us through our interactions with you, including through our website, blog, through our customer service representatives, through our sales representatives, through contests/sweepstakes, at events, through mobile applications, and through third parties.

You may elect not to provide certain information, which could result in you not being able to take advantage of certain capabilities of this website, our mobile applications or other services we offer.

We may request, collect and store some or all of the following types of personal information: your name, billing address, shipping address, e-mail address, location, telephone number, financial and payment information, including your credit card number and expiration date, date of birth, and any information about a third party you provide accessing the website. If you access our website or mobile applications with your log-in credentials from a social networking site (e.g. Facebook, Google, or Twitter) or if you otherwise agree to associate your account with us with a social networking site, we may receive personal information about you from such social networking site, in accordance with the terms of use and privacy policy of such social networking site. This may include your email address, public profile (including your name, profile picture, gender, age, and the names of your other “friends” on such social networking sites). We may add this to the information we have already collected from you via other interactions. 

**Automatically Collected Information**

We collect and store certain other non-personally identifiable information automatically whenever you interact with us. For example, we may collect your Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser information and reference site domain name when you visit this website.  We may analyze this data for preferences, trends, and site usage statistics.

Other information we may collect includes your behavior on our site. We use this information to improve the user experience. This may include, but is not limited to: your activities and clicks on our website, maps accessed, comments, tags, notifications, and shares. This information may also include your interactions with other users on our site.

  We may also collect information by using cookies, web beacons, and related technologies in order to analyze and understand how the website is used and to improve your visits to the website. For example, we may use cookies and related technologies to: (i) customize account pages for you, (ii) track user visits and account features, (iii) determine what features and pages are most frequently requested or visited, and (iv) save your password so you do not have to provide it each time you visit the website.

  "Cookies" are small text files that a website sends to a user's hard drive through the browser for data storage. Most browsers accept cookies automatically but allow you to disable them. By disabling or otherwise rejecting cookies, you may not be able to take full advantage of all offerings on this website. We recommend that you leave cookies "turned on" so that we can offer you a better overall experience on this website.

  We use third-party companies to provide Internet data hosting and to help us measure and determine how visitors use our website and to evaluate the effectiveness of our website and promotions so that we can improve and optimize our website and the products and services we offer. We may use third-party companies to serve advertisements (banners or links) on our behalf throughout the Internet. These companies use tracking technologies (including cookies and pixel tags) to collect non-identifiable information about your visits to our website and your interactions with our products and services. 

  Our websites currently do not have a mechanism to recognize “Do Not Track” signals, but several of the third-party companies who utilize these cookies or beacons enable you to opt out of this advertising. If you wish to opt out of receiving this third-party interest-based advertising, you may obtain more information [HERE](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/). Please note this does not opt you out of receiving marketing communications from us.

Some of our e-mail communications to you may include a "click-through URL" linked to a particular page on the website. By clicking on one of these URLs, you will automatically enter our website and we may collect information related to the "click-through." You may avoid having this information collected by not clicking on URL links in our e-mail communications.

**How Do I Indicate Whether Or Not I Want To Receive Promotional Communications?** **  
 **  
You will be able to change your email preferences for receiving promotional emails by clicking on an "unsubscribe" hyperlink contained in promotional e-mails we send you. Please note that removal of personal information from our database or "opting-out" will not stop marketing or advertising content that is generated for distribution or is otherwise queued for transmission to you prior to the time when we can implement your request. 

If you establish an account, you may receive certain types of communications even if you have not opted-in to receive them because these types of communications may be necessary in order to maintain an account on the website.

  **Information from Other Sources    
**   
We may collect information about you from third-party sources and information that is publicly available. For example, information you submit in a public forum (e.g., a blog, chat room, or social network site) can be read, collected, or used by us and others, and could be used to personalize your experience. You are responsible for the information you choose to submit in these instances. Another example, is that we may receive demographic information about you from a third party to make our service and marketing efforts more efficient and personalized for you.  

  **HOW IS YOUR INFORMATION USED?    
**   
We use the personal information we collect to communicate with you, analyze and develop our business, and to improve our products, services, and interactions with customers. We, or third-party service providers we engage, may use the information to provide services that you have requested, provide customer service, respond to your comments, questions or complaints, personalize your interactions with us, identify your preferences and online browsing habits, analyze trends and statistics, create, administer and fulfill our contests and other promotions, evaluate and improve the website and our services, and prepare and send you information regarding our services. We also use your information for business purposes such as security, legal compliance, payment processing, analytics, operations, fraud detection, reporting, and making back-ups. 

    We may display personal testimonials/reviews of satisfied customers on our site in addition to other endorsements. With your consent we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at support@2modern.com.

  **WITH WHOM DO WE SHARE THIS INFORMATION?**

Except with your consent or as described in this Privacy Policy, we do not sell, rent, or share with third parties any of your personal information.

We may share personal information with certain third parties that perform services on our behalf. The services provided by those third parties may include: operating or hosting the website, providing the products and services you request, authorization and processing of your payments, product fulfillment, fraud protection and credit risk reduction, product customization, marketing and promotional material distribution, loyalty program management, promotions fulfillment, web site evaluation, data analysis and, where applicable, data cleansing. Those third parties are not authorized to use or disclose personal information you provide to us on or through this website for any purpose other than to perform the services designated by us.

We may share personal information with a third party if we are required by law to disclose that personal information. For example, we may be required to disclose personal information to respond to a subpoena, court order or other legal process. We may also disclose this information in response to a law enforcement agency's request, or if we believe disclosure is necessary to investigate or address unlawful acts or acts that may endanger the health or safety of a consumer or the general public, to verify or enforce compliance with the terms of use and policies that govern our website or as otherwise required or permitted by law. In addition, the personal information you provide to us may be transferred as an asset in connection with a merger or sale involving all or part of the 2Modern website or as part of a corporate reorganization, stock sale or other change of control.

  **WHAT ABOUT THE PRIVACY OF CHILDREN UNDER 13?  **

  We do not intend to collect personal information from anyone who is under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13 you should not provide any personal information to us and you should use this website only with the involvement of a parent or guardian. If you are a parent or guardian of a child under the age of 13 and suspect he/she has provided personal information on or through the website, please contact us as set forth below under the section entitled "How Can I Contact You Regarding This Privacy Policy?"

**HOW DO WE KEEP PERSONAL INFORMATION SECURE?    
**   
The security of your information is very important to us. We have instituted several measures and security procedures to protect our servers and networks that store personal information. However, no transmission of information over the Internet is 100% secure and, therefore, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information. In order to help protect personal information you provide to us: (i) you should not share your password or account information with anyone else, (ii) you should use a secure web browser, and (iii) you should change your password often. If you wish to cancel a password, or if you become aware of any loss, theft, or unauthorized use of a password, please contact us as set forth below under "How Can I Contact You Regarding This Privacy Policy?"

**TrustGuard & Global Sign**

Our website utilizes the latest technology for shopping and e-commerce security. We have multiple layers of protection from the best security-providers the internet has to offer, and we are certified by both TrustGuard and Global Sign.

When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol. All of your personal information, including your credit card information and sign-in password, are stored in encrypted format at all times.

**HOW CAN I ACCESS, CORRECT, AND UPDATE PERSONAL INFORMATION?    
**   
You may access, correct and update certain personal information that you have provided to us by clicking on the "My Account" area of this website and following the instructions set forth therein or by contacting us with your request as set forth below under the section entitled "How Can I Contact You Regarding This Privacy Policy?"

We reserve the right to retain any personal information reasonably necessary to appropriately document our business activities and for record retention purposes. We will store personal information for as long as is reasonably necessary for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. You may find out more details regarding this Privacy Policy by contacting us as provided below under "How Can I Contact You Regarding This Privacy Policy?"

**WHAT HAPPENS WHEN I LINK TO OR FROM ANOTHER WEBSITE?  **

  This website may contain links to or from websites to which this Privacy Policy does not apply ("Linked Websites"). Please be advised that the practices described in this Privacy Policy do not reflect the practices regarding information collection, use and disclosure of Linked Websites or the owners or operators of those Linked Websites. Your use of Linked Websites will be governed by the terms of use, privacy policies, and other terms, notices, and policies set forth or referenced in those Linked Websites. We encourage you to be aware that when you leave this website you should read the privacy policies of each and every website that you visit to ensure protection of your information. 

**Changes to this Statement**

2Modern will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. 2Modern encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Company is protecting your information

**WHAT IF I AM AN INTERNATIONAL USER?**

Our digital operations are conducted, in whole or in part, in the United States. Regardless of where you live, you consent to have your personal data transferred, processed, and stored in the United States, and allow 2Modern to use and collect your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

**HOW CAN I CONTACT YOU REGARDING THIS PRIVACY POLICY?    
**   
If you have any questions or concerns regarding your privacy or the Privacy Policy you can send a request with your concerns or any further questions to us by using the contact information provided below:

By Email: support@2modern.com  
Subject:  Privacy Policy Questions

By Mail:  
Carve Media, Inc. (dba 2Modern)

35 Miller Ave

Mill Valley, CA, 94941

Effective as of May 15, 2017
